livepage.gr 2008-12-17

# MyLivePage.com : Main Page / About / Privacy

**Information Collection & Use**

_**Registration**_

In order to become a member of this Web site, you must first complete the registration form. During registration you are required to give personal information (such as name and email address). We use this information to contact you about the services on our site in which you have expressed interest. 

You have the option to provide demographic information (such as income level and gender) to us; we encourage you to submit this information so we can provide you a more personalized experience on our site. 

At certain times MyLivePage may send you newsletters and information about present and new services, as well as advertisements from selected commercial partners. You will have the option to opt-out of these services. 

We also use this information to decide which advertisements from selected commercial partners might be of interest to you or the visitors of your personal site. However, we will not disclose your personal information directly to our commercial partners. 

MLP N.V. is the sole owner of the information collected on MyLivePage.com. MLP N.V. collects personally identifiable information from our users at several different points on our Web site. 

**_Orders_**

If you purchase a product or service from us, we – and/or our payment service partner - request certain personally identifiable information from you on our order form. You must provide contact information (such as name, email, and shipping address) and financial information (such as credit card number, expiration date). 

We use this information for billing purposes and to fill your orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we will use this information to contact you. 

**_Surveys or Contests_**

From time-to-time we may provide you the opportunity to participate in contests or surveys on our site. If you participate, we will request certain personally identifiable information from you. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. The requested information typically includes contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code). 

We may use a third party service provider to conduct these surveys or contests; that company will be prohibited from using our users’ personally identifiable information for any other purpose. We will not share the personally identifiable information you provide through a contest or survey with other third parties unless we give you prior notice and choice. 

**_Tell-A-Friend_**

If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our site, we will ask you for your friend’s name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. MLP N.V. stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email and tracking the success of our referral program. 

Your friend may contact us at info@mylivepage.com to request that we remove this information from our database. 

**Communications from the Site**

**_Special Offers and Updates_**

Out of respect for your privacy, we present the option not to receive these types of communications. You will find this option at the bottom of the email. 

**_Newsletters_**

We will use your name and email address to send newsletters to you. Out of respect for your privacy, we provide you a way to unsubscribe. 

Service-related Announcements We will send you strictly service-related announcements on rare occasions when it is necessary to do so. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance, we might send you an email. 

Generally, you may not opt-out of these communications, which are not promotional in nature. If you do not wish to receive them, you have the option to deactivate your account. 

Customer Service Based upon the personally identifiable information you provide us, we will send you a welcoming email to verify your username, password and email. We will also communicate with you in response to your inquiries, to provide the services you request, and to manage your account. We will communicate with you by email. 

**_Profile_**

We store information that we collect through cookies, log files, clear gifs, [and/or third party sources] to create a “profile” of your preferences. We tie your personally identifiable information, and your purchasing history, to information in the profile, in order to provide tailored promotions and marketing offers and to improve the content of the site for you. 

We do not share more information than that is visible on your public profile with other third parties. 

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**

**_Aggregate Information (non-personally identifiable)_**

We share aggregated demographic information about our user base with our partners and advertisers. This information does not identify individual users. 

**_Personally identifiable information:_**

We DO NOT Share Personally Identifiable Information with Third Parties 

**_Agents_**

We use an outside shipping company to fulfill orders, and a credit card processing company to bill you for goods and services. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any other purposes. 

**_Service Providers_**

We might use other third parties to provide certain services on our site. When you sign up for these services we will share the information as necessary for the third party to provide that service. 

**_Other Third Parties_**

MLP N.V. is free to share your personal information with parent and daughter companies within the MyLivePage group. 

**_Legal Disclaimer_**

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site 

**_Choice/Opt-out_**

We provide you the opportunity to ‘opt-out’ of having your personally identifiable information used for certain purposes, when we ask for this information. For example, if you purchase a product/service but do not wish to receive any additional marketing material from us, you can indicate your preference on our order form. 

If you no longer wish to receive our newsletter and promotional communications, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included in each newsletter or communication or by emailing us at info@mylivepage.com. 

You will be notified when your personal information is collected by any third party that is not our agent/service provider, so you can make an informed choice as to whether or not to share your information with that party. 

**Log Files**

As is true of most Web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data. 

We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. 

We might link this automatically-collected data to personally identifiable information. 

**Cookies**

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user’s computer for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies on this site. We link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site. 

We use both session ID cookies and/or persistent cookies. A session ID cookie expires when you close you browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser’s “help” file. 

We set a persistent cookie to store your passwords, so you don’t have to enter it more than once. Persistent cookies also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. 

If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some areas of our site, such as contests or surveys, will be limited. 

Some of our business partners (e.g., advertisers) use cookies on our site. We have no access to or control over these cookies. See “Third Party Advertisers.” 

This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by MyLivePage.com only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers. 

**Third Party Advertisers**

The ads appearing on this Web site are delivered to users by our advertising partners. We share Web site usage information about users only with reputable third parties for the purpose of targeting our Internet banner advertisements on this site. 

Our commercial partners might use cookies and clear GIFs on this site, which allow it to recognize a user's cookie when a user visits this site. The information collected and shared through this technology is not personally identifiable. 

**Links to Other Sites**

This Web site contains links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by MLP N.V.. Please be aware that we, MLP N.V., are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. 

We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. 

This privacy statement applies only to information collected by this Web site. 

**Bulletin Boards/Chat Rooms/Profile Page**

If you use a bulletin board, chat room or public profile page on this site, you should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by other users of these forums, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these forums, rooms or pages. 

**Access to Personally Identifiable Information**

If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update or deactivate it by making the change on our member information page, or by emailing our Customer Support at support@mylivepage.com. 

**Security**

The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card number and/or social security number) on our registration or order forms, we or our payment service partner encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). 

We and our payment service partner follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. 

If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can send email us at info@mylivepage.com 

**Business Transitions**

In the event MLP N.V. goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your personally identifiable information will likely be among the assets transferred. You will be notified via email of any such change in ownership or control of your personal information. 

Changes in this Privacy Statement If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. 

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page. 

Contact Us If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at: info@mylivepage.com 

[Comments: 0](http://en.mylivepage.com/wiki/11/132) Views: 12986 Size:12340 byte  
Last changes are made by: [](http://mombra.mylivepage.com/)

[mombra](http://mombra.mylivepage.com/) 153 days ago  Posted by|  Text  
---|---  
No comments
